Thank you so much for getting my bags back.
非常感谢你 对于把我的包弄回来
We aim to please.
我们目标在于 使满意.
Do you have my booking? Yamamoto?
你们有我的预定吗? Yamamoto?
How do you spell that, please?  Y-A-M-A-M-O-T-O.
你怎么拼写它,请问?  Y-A-M-A-M-O-T-O.
Here we are. That's a suite on the 24th floor, with a lovely view of the park.
找到了! 是一个套房 在24楼, 带有一个好看的视野  公园的.
-Great.  -And we're connecting the computer, fax machine,
-很好.  -并且我们正在连接电脑, 传真机,
and extra phone in your room right now.
和额外的电话 在你房间 此刻.
Very good. Here's my card.
非常好. 这是我的卡.
Can you tell me the hotel phone and fax numbers, please?
你能告诉我 酒店的电话和传真号码吗, 请?
Of course. The hotel phone is area code 617 437 1890.
当然了.酒店的电话是 区号 617 437 1890.
Your fax number is 617 437 1888.
你的传真号码是 617 437 1888.
617 437 1888. Thank you.
617 437 1888. 谢谢你.
Your card and your key, Mr. Yamamoto.
你的卡 和你的钥匙, Yamamoto先生.
Room 2422. Carl? Carl... that way!
房间2422. Carl? Carl(朝)那边!